Contact

pamgrigg2@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/pamelagrigg-514b0267 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

CHTP Certified Healing Touch Practitioner

CMSRN certified Med/Surg RN BSN

Pamela Grigg

RN at Scripps Mercy San Diego, Certified Healing Touch Instructor Greater San Diego Area

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Patient Advocacy, Nursing Education, Medical-Surgical, Holistic Health, and Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS). Strong healthcare services professional with a BSN focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from SDSU. Certified Bio Energy Practitioner (Healing Touch), Certified Holistic Nurse, Certified Holistic Nurse Coach with a focus on mind, body, spirit connection, with a goal to help individuals to embrace and enhance their own Self-Empowerment and Well-Being.

Experience

Scripps Mercy San Diego

RN

2009 - Present (11 years)

Trauma RN with involvement in helping to develop Holistic Integrative Health Care

Exterior Design

Landscape owner

1986 - 2008 (22 years)

Owner, designer, construction

Education

San Diego State University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2006 - 2009)

Grossmont College

Associate of Science - AS, Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2005 - 2006)

Cyamaca College
Ornamental Horticulture

SDSU

BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse

San Diego State University-California State University